Keep running along, watch as we pass by,
as we raise our flag, up high in the sky.
Alright,
here we go now, sailing through the
endless ocean, facing all that comes by.
Let's look for our treasure nobody has
ever got to witness with their own eyes.
All we have to do is keep believing in our
dreams, And let our heart lead the way!
Then once we got all the
others left is to go,
When we face the dark and stormy weather?
Keep the pace, we'll
link our hearts together!
Then I'm sure we'll make it through!
No matter what!
Keep running along, keep running along!
Still raising our flag as we journey on!
Though our chances are close to
none, We won't back down from anyone!
Let's start off the chase,
let's start off the chase!
Toward our own dreams,
while keeping the pace!
With a compass pointing to our goal!
We won't stop till we've
gone around the world!
Start me up!
Keep running along, keep running along!
And we'll never stop,
till we're at the top!
There's no way that we'll ever quit!
Won't keep heading for tomorrow!
Let's start up the chase,
let's start up the chase!
I see through your eyes
what we'll have to face!
All the memories we'll say in our hearts!
We'll never let them go!
Brand new world!
Let's start me up!
Too close!
What's the deal with them
shooting their own ships?
Are they that dumb?
Oh great, I got small again!
Third gear is a pretty cool
idea and it is really powerful!
But talk about lousy side effects!
I was pumped up and
big for about a minute!
So I guess I'll He'll be
shrunk down for a minute, too.
I gotta hide till this wears off
or he'll stomp on me like a bug!
Is that a side effect or
some kind of bad joke?
Whatever it is, he's still alive.
Well, this would have been a waste of
time if he died in a measly cannon attack.
Look, everyone!
You can see the front gate!
We're almost there! Yeah!
Keep running!
You remember your old pal, Franky, right?
He got taken away by the
bad guys too, like Tom.
So you up for a fight or what?
Your precious Straw Hat was
rampaging aboard that battleship,
and now he's a pile of ashes!
Your captain is dead.
Go ahead and give up already!
What the hell?
That ship was filled with their own men.
You're starting to understand the
merciless nature of the buster.
Call this is the face of justice.
Cutty Flam.
Now do yourself a favor
and hand over Nico Robin.
If you cooperate with us, I'll see to
it that you'll pardon for your crimes.
Why are you even bothering
to protect this woman?
Anyway, what's in it for you?
You're not even a pirate.
The world government is
devoted to protecting
normal citizens like you
from people like her.
Do you really trust her more than us?
This woman with blood on her hands.
If you choose to defy us, well
you remember what happened to Tom.
AAAAAAAH!
OOH! OOH!
OOH!
My... face...
I didn't think I could
get any more swollen...
Aw, crap!
He's using the elephant sword!
That thing's unstoppable!
Okay, listen, Funnfried, this
has gone on for far too long.
I want you to fatally wound
Mikko-Robin while her guard is down.
Take this!
Elevator!
Bastard!
He stopped it!
You just keep digging your
grave deeper and deeper
What are you doing, Von Freed?
You're an elephant, dammit!
How are you losing?
Get mad and slice them caprici!
You best make your nose
normal again, elephant?
Unless you want a couple of new
nostrils in the middle of your forehead!
Okay.
Okay, there you go. Smart move.
Nico Robin, you think Straw Hat
and the others are still coming?
Without a doubt.
They'll be here.
I already told you once before that
I'm betting everything on them Spanda.
You what?
Funny.
I never dreamed this
day would actually come.
If I'd only had the power
before, it wouldn't even be here.
I'm amending the charges.
For the crime of designing and
building a ship for Gold Roger,
the king of the pirates,
Tom and Tom alone will be apprehended
and taken to Annie's lobby.
That is all.
What in the hell got into that
old geezer's head? Whatever.
I don't need his lackeys.
Release those two apprentices!
Tom can't be saved from this.
It's the government we're up against.
There's nothing we can do. Endure it.
Tom traded his life for yours.
If you make them your enemy,
you won't be able to win, no matter
how many lives you have to give.
Benny's lobby is the government's
personal judicial island.
Not one single person who's been sent to
that dreadful place has
ever been seen again.
He's out of his mind!
What should we do, sir?
Are you out of your mind, too?
We keep on going.
That's what he wants us to do, right?
Don't worry about him. Right. Yes, sir.
All right, Puppetop, that's far enough.
What do you think you're doing?
Where are you taking your creator?
Get him! Get him!
Get him!
I won't let you pass!
Give me Tom back!
Even if it killed me, I had
to stop them from taking Tom.
Everyone knows the
reputation of any slobby.
And everyone knows the power
of the world government.
But the Straw Hats didn't care.
They knew what they were up
against, and they still pressed on.
In order to save their friend,
they were willing to take on the
entire world without hesitation.
And that's my kind of people.
I've never forgotten the role you
played in Tom's death, and I never will.
Every time I pictured your stupid
face, I dreamt of smashing it.
Smashing your face!
What are you doing?
Don't come any closer!
Stop this!
Until there was nothing
left but bloody hamburger!
That's a pretty good start.
Thanks to the Straw Hats, I
finally get to live out this dream.
How about some weapons?
I died before and it wasn't that bad.
I'll do whatever it takes to
get the Straw Hats out of here,
even if it means me
dying for a second time.
Hand over your escort ship right now.
I'm making them an escape
route and you're helping.
And I'm helping too.
I'm alright now.
Don't look back. Just go.
If you stay on this island, you'll die.
Take my raft and go out to sea.
But what about you?
He's got me, little lady.
I'm afraid this is the end. Hurry! No!
Everybody I care about is here!
This is different.
This is nothing like Ohara.
And I've got nothing to
be afraid of this time.
I'm not alone. This time.
I've got my friends.
He sniffed me out.
So that power of yours
demands as much as it gives.
Seems like a pretty fair trade, though.
One must always pay a great
price for a great power.
Life returned paper art fighting for.
FINGER PISTOLS!
Time to give up.
If you continue these ridiculous
attacks, I'll have to...
I can't move!
Not good, dumb man.
I apologize, but I've got to
kill you in that stupid form.
Now, die!
Finger pistol! Spots!
Sheep's back body!
Come on, hurry up or we're gonna die!
That blow from earlier damaged my legs.
Hey, it's changing. I'm changing back.
You see?
It worked.
Looks like I messed you up after all.
Is there really nothing we can do?
I've got to think of something.
If I don't, then we're all going to drown.
And we haven't even made
sure that Robin is safe yet.
Is this really the end?
I suppose I have lived a good life.
There's no denying that
I've had some fun times.
No, I'm not ready to die!
I can't drown in a tunnel.
This is not a fitting gift for
the brave warrior of the sea.
Usam.
I can't hold my breath any longer.
It hurts too much.
Everything's starting to go dark.
Someone help!
It's alright.
Just hang in there.
I'm not going to let you die.
What?
What's going on?
It feels like something's pulling me.
Am I hallucinating?
That's gotta be it.
It's just like those old
tales that sailors talk about.
Just before they drown, they
see an elegant tail fin.
They look up, surprised
to see long, flowing hair.
I've never seen anything so beautiful.
It's like she's something out of a dream.
A legendary mermaid.
If I'm dying, and this is just a dream,
then I don't want to wake up.
I'm running as fast as
this tail will let me!
None of you are going to die on my watch!
She's the mermaid!
Sorry, boys, but me and the Straw
Hats will be taking this boat.
Gotta escape somehow, you know?
And so,
after cleaning house a bit, what was once
an escort ship is now our escape ship.
Handy.
Now we wait.
Once the others get here, we'll split.
What's that?
Everyone!
Don't you die on me?
Hurry!
The main gates are just ahead!
We're almost off this island!
It shows a little further! Run, Giants!
Give it all you've got!
Just leave it to us!
We can finally get out of here!
We're gonna be safe!
Be to the other side!
Giant doors!
Don't do nothing when
you've got giant muscles!
Three freaking battleships
must have been waiting for us.
Look, they made it out.
How'd they get free?
We left them tied up in the courthouse.
They're stronger than we thought.
Vice admiral, sir.
I know.
Aim the cannons at them. Sir,
state your unit, your marine code,
and have your picture ID ready to
show before you can board the ship?
You're good. Go on.
Oh, what a relief.
I thought we were gonna
go down with the island
Resistance is futile, pirates.
You make one move, and
we'll empty our ammo on you.
This couldn't get any worse! Oh, man.
I doubt they're gonna offer us amnesty.
And we can't go back.
The island's burning.
We've got nowhere we can run to.
Every one of their weapons,
all of them, aimed at us!
So what's going through
your head right now, huh?
I'm thinking back on my life.
You shouldn't talk like that.
It's either that, or what.
What comes next?
The afterlife.
Get out!
All of our remaining
personnel have boarded.
All ships, retreat to
a safe firing distance.
They're not really going
to shoot us, right?
Sir, battleships 6,
7 and 8 have identified
and reported a large
number of pirates located
in front of the main gate
Hey, all of you, wake up!
Come on! Say something!
They made it.
They're all still alive.
It's a miracle.
I can't believe it.
They must have seen something down there
that put them all in a state of shock.
Whatever it was, it saved their lives.
If they hadn't passed out, they would
have swallowed enough water to kill them.
Well, either way, they're still alive.
Though it does make you
wonder what they could
have seen down there that
spooked them so much?
I bet it was you!
Well, Lock there.
You're the one that pirate king boy
wanted to rescue so bad, aren't you?
Yeah, I remember now.
We met at the ship station.
These Straw Hats are something else.
Back then, I never would have thought you
guys could pull off a stunt like this.
If you don't hurry up and put some damn
clothes on, I'll gouge my eyes out.
When he said he was going to be king of
the pirates, I gotta admit, I laughed.
Our Gourmet is counting on us!
We're leaving now!
But now after everything that's
happened, I bet he can actually do it
Is...
is Nami okay?
As lively as ever.
You guys are tough.
Welcome to the land of the living.
It wasn't a nightmare!
Mermaids really don't exist!
So all those old sailor stories are true.
Every time you think you see a
mermaid, it's actually a dugong.
Shut up, you bastard.
She hasn't even confessed
to being a mermaid yet.
Stop trying to kill my fantasies.
If you want to be specific,
I'm an ice fish mermaid.
Stop it!
Don't say another word!
There's no way!
What kind of mermaid lives on
dry land and has legs and feet?
I refuse to accept this!
Just to educate you boys, when we
mermaids get to be about 30 years old,
our tail fin forks in two and we can
walk on land like a regular old human.
If you ever make it out to Fishman
Island, you'll see what I'm talking about.
Their tail split?
Oh, I get it.
I heard the same thing happens to a
cat's tail if they live to be a hundred.
Then they become goblins.
Ah, so she's a goblin cat.
Don't lump mermaids in
with those monsters.
Enough about that.
Where are your manners?
Didn't I just save your lives?
Thank you, Granny Kaku.
We appreciate it.
Don't mention it.
Oh, what happened where am I?
Yes,
because of all of you!
Thank you so much!
I
always
did
think it was weird
that you have fins and scales.
Now I know why!
How many clues does it take?
Hey, what's wrong?
Are you all right?
I...
I can't move my body.
I'm not surprised.
Don't worry about it.
I'll explain everything later, okay?
Hey, Zoro!
Zoro!
I mean, uh, swordsman!
Over here, take a look.
Hard to believe that's the same
island we were on not long ago.
What's going on?
What's up with this attack?
It's like a sea of flames out there!
I noticed something else.
It seems kind of like they're trying
to avoid firing where Nico Robin's at.
That would explain why this
bridge hasn't been blown to bits.
If they don't want to kill her, then
they still intend on getting her back.
After the Marines are done
attacking Eni's lobby,
they'll probably come after us with
some hand-to-hand combat to reclaim her.
I don't like the sound of that.
We're at our limit here.
On top of that,
those battleships are bound to have
some pretty powerful guys on board.
Where's Luffy right now?
From where I last saw him
and what's left standing,
I'd say he's there, the
first tower of that bridge.
He's fighting that damn pigeon guy.
You know, Rob Lucci.
That's close by.
We should go help him.
No, don't bother.
That pigeon bastard he's
fighting is no ordinary man.
No good could come of it.
If we get caught up in that
mess, who knows what'll happen.
Those battleships could
turn this way at any time.
We need to make sure we
still have an escape route.
The plan is to stay
here and wait for Luffy.
It's the best we can do.
The storm is just beginning.
Understood.
Hey, Franky.
Think your friends are okay?
Are you serious?
Nothing can stop the Franky family.
Don't you worry.
I'm sure they got away.
Hey! Paulie!
What are you doing?
A transponder snail?
What the hell are you
going to do with that?
We need to find out how the
Straw Hats are holding up.
Big Brow! No!
This is gonna be the last time!
I won't stop until I bring you down.
You hear me your body
can't take this you'll kill
yourself Maybe I guess there's
only one way to find out.
Now second gear